Guide to the James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Jones, Mrs. Thomas E. (GNJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, funds for participation in Oxford Conference See: Embree, Edwin R. (JWJ)
White, George (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, health of See: Wright, Louis T. (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, leave of absence from N.A.A.C.P. (1929) See: Spingarn, Joel E. (JWJ)
James Weldon Johnson, lecture folder See: Viking Press - Marshall Best (1930-33) (JWJ)
Encyclopedia of the Negro See: DuBois, William E.B. (JWJ)
Logan, Rayford (JWJ)
Stokes, Anson Phelps (JWJ)
Woodson, Carter G. (JWJ)
Ethiopia, invasion by Italy, Afro-American reaction to See: Jones, William N. (JWJ)
"Fifty Years", by James Weldon Johnson See: Stokes, Anson Phelps (JWJ)
GNJ - James Weldon Johnson to (undated) (FC)
Fisk University, James Weldon Johnson at [Note: material related to Fisk University is located throughout the correspondence. ] See: Johnson, Charles S. (JWJ)
Jones, Thomas E. (JWJ)
Jones, Mrs. Thomas E. (GNJ)
Fisk University, use of James Weldon Johnson's Negro Americans, What Now? for fund raising See: Viking Press - Marshall Best (1934-68) (JWJ)
Friends of Haiti Society See: White, Walter (1938) (JWJ)
Garland Fund See: American Fund for Public Service
God's Trombones, by James Weldon Johnson See: Lambert, Constant (JWJ)
Viking Press (JWJ)
God's Trombones, by James Weldon Johnson, the title of See: Spencer, Anne (JWJ)
Spingarn, Arthur B. (JWJ)
Spingarn, Joel E. (JWJ)
Goyescas, by Fernando Periquet, English Libretto by James Weldon Johnson See: Periquet, Fernando (JWJ)
Gruening, Ernest, recommendation as United States ambassador to Haiti See: White, Walter (1932) (JWJ)
Haiti See: Moton, Robert Russa (JWJ)
White, Walter (1934) (JWJ)
White, Walter (1938) (JWJ)
Haiti, proposed United States ambassador to (1932) See: White, Walter (1932) (JWJ)
Haiti, United States minister to (1915) See: DuBois, William E.B. (JWJ)
Haiti, United States occupation of and James Weldon Johnson's articles about conditions of See: Carr, Wilbur J. (JWJ)
Gruening, Ernest H. (JWJ)
Haiti (JWJ)
Holly, Alonzo P.B. (JWJ)
McCormick, Mendill (JWJ)
Metropolitan Magazine (JWJ)
Ovington, Mary White (JWJ)
Schoenrich, Otto (JWJ)
Harlem Hospital See: White, Walter (1933) (JWJ)
Harlem Renaissance, James Weldon Johnson's comments on (1933) See: West, Dorothy (JWJ)
Harlem riots, reaction to (1935) See: White, Walter (1935) (JWJ)
Hayden, Robert, publication of poems by See: Knopf, Alfred A. (JWJ)
Viking Press - Marshall Best (JWJ)
Hicks, [Rev. John H.], (dean, Atlanta University) See: Scoville, William L. (JWJ)
Hoover, Herbert, nomination by Republican Party (1932) See: Ickes, Harold L. (JWJ)
Hope, John, provisions for the widow of See: Bethune, Mary McLeod (JWJ)
Lampkin, Daisy E. (JWJ)
Hope, John See: Atlanta University, the presidency of and Affiliation with Morehouse College and Spelman College (1929)]
Houston, Charles H., employment by the N.A.A.C.P. See: White, Walter (1934) (JWJ)
Howard University See: Napier, James C. (JWJ)
Hughes, Charles Evans, campaign for the presidency (1916) See: Hughes, Charles Evans (sec.) (JWJ)
Hughes, Langston, application for fellowship from Guggenheim Foundation See: Guggenheim Foundation (JWJ)
Hurston, Zora Neale, proposed experimental theatre at Fisk University See: Jones, Thomas E. (JWJ)
Hurston, Zora Neale, proposed study at Yale School of Drama See: Jones, Thomas E. (JWJ)
Imperialiam See: Haiti, United States occupation of and James Weldon Johnson's articles about the conditions of
Imperialiam, Italy's invasion of Ethiopia, Afro-American reaction to See: Jones, William N. (JWJ)
Institute of Pacific Relations, Kyoto Conference (1929) See: Institute of Pacific Relations (JWJ)
GNJ - James Weldon Johnson to (1929) (FC)
Institute of Race Relations See: Bryan, Helen R. (JWJ)
Johnson, Charles S. (JWJ)
International Labor Defense See: Pickens, William (JWJ)
See also: Scottsboro case
James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection, Yale University See: James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection (GNJ)
Van Vechten, Carl (1945-64) (GNJ)
James Weldon Johnson Memorial Committee See: Randolph, Richetta G. (GNJ)
Van Vechten, Carl (1939) (GNJ)
White, Walter (GNJ)
Johnson, James (father of James Weldon Johnson) the estate of See: L'Engle, E.J. (JWJ)
GNJ - James Weldon Johnson to (FC)
JWJ - Agnes M. Edwards to (FC)
JWJ - Grace Nail Johnson to (FC)
JWJ - Helen Louise Johnson to (FC)
JWJ - J. Rosamond Johnson to (FC)
JWJ - John E. Nail to (FC)
Johnson, James Weldon, lyrics by See: American Guild of Authors and Composers (JWJ)
Edward B. Marks Music Co. (JWJ)
G. Ricordi and Co., Inc. (JWJ)
GNJ - James Weldon Johnson to (1914-18) (FC)
GNJ - J. Rosamond Johnson to (FC)
JWJ - Grace Nail Johnson to (1914-18) (FC)
JWJ - J. Rosamond Johnson to (FC)
JRJ - royalty statements (FC)
Johnson, James Weldon, proposed as Republican candidate for United States House of Representatives See: Koening, Samuel S. (JWJ)
Travis, Hamilton J. (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, resignation of secretaryship of N.A.A.C.P. See: N.A.A.C.P. - National Office (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, speaking engagements See: Adult Education Council of Chicago (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, "To What Extent Do You Think American Negroes Should Interest Themselves in Abyssinia?" draft and copy of JWJ's comments on question See: Jones, William N. (JWJ)
Johnson, James Weldon, withdrawl of appointment to Labor Policy Board of Work Projects Administration See: Baker, Jacob (JWJ)
White, Walter (1935) (JWJ)
Krehbiel, H.E., controversy with James Weldon Johnson See: Letters to the Editor (JWJ)
Peacock, Roscoe (JWJ)
Randolph, Richetta G. (JWJ)
Kyoto Conference (1929) See: Institute of Pacific Relations (JWJ)
GNJ - James Weldon Johnson to (1929) (JWJ)
Labor movements, Brookwood Labor School See: American Fund for Public Service (JWJ)
Brookwood Labor School (JWJ)
Labor movements, International Labor Defense See: Pickens, William (JWJ)
See also: Scottsboro case
Labor unions, blacks and See: American Fund for Public Service (JWJ)
Randolph, Asa Philip (JWJ)
League of Negro Writers See: McKay, Claude (JWJ)
Liberia, reaction to Firestone's relationship with See: Graves, Anna Melissa (JWJ)
"Lift Every Voice and Sing", by James Weldon Johnson and J. Rosamond Johnson See: Edward B. Marks Music Co. (JWJ)
Scott, Emmett J. (JWJ)
Lynching and anti-lynching legislation See: Alexander, Will W. (JWJ)
DuBois, William E.B. (JWJ)
Hamilton, John D. (JWJ)
Randolph, Richetta G. (1921-29) (JWJ)
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (JWJ)
Daily American (Jacksonville, Fla.); African American authors -- 20th Century -- Archives; African American civil rights workers; African American educators; African Americans -- Civil rights -- History -- 20th Century; African Americans -- Social life and customs; American literature -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Civil Rights movements -- United States -- History -- 20th Century; Civil rights workers -- United States; Diplomatic and consular service, American; Dramatists, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Harlem Renaissance -- Archives; Lyricists -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets -- 20th Century -- Archives; United States -- Race relations; Ambrotypes (photographs); Audiotapes; Audiovisual materials; Daguerreotypes (photographs); Diaries; Phonograph records; Photographic prints; Scrapbooks; Tintypes (prints); Authors; Studio portraits; Braithwaite, William Stanley, 1878-1962; Brawley, Benjamin, 1882-1939; Brown, Charlotte Hawkins, 1883-1961; Brown, Sterling A., 1901-1989; Brownlee, Frederick Leslie, 1883-1962; Bryan, Henry Lewis, 1853-1934; Cullen, Countee, 1903-1946; Du Bois, W. E. B. (William Edward Burghardt), 1868-1963; Holmes, John Haynes, 1879-1964; Hope, John, 1868-1936; Hughes, Langston, 1902-1967; Hurston, Zora Neale, 1891-1960; Johnson, Charles Spurgeon, 1893-1956; Johnson, Grace Nail, 1885-1976; Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954; Johnson, James Weldon, 1871-1938; Jones, Thomas Elsa, 1888-1973; Knopf, Alfred A., 1892-1984; Knopf, Blanche W., 1894-1966; Larsen, Nella, 1891-1964; Matthews, Brander, 1852-1929; McKay, Claude, 1890-1948; Mencken, H. L. (Henry Louis), 1880-1956; Moton, Robert Russa, 1867-1940; Okala, Ollie Jewell Sims, 1908-2001; Ovington, Mary White, 1865-1951; Payne, E. George (Enoch George), 1877-1953; Pickens, William, 1881-1954; Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison), 1906-1978; Schomburg, Arthur Alfonso, 1874-1938; Scott, Emmett J. (Emmett Jay), 1873-1957; Spencer, Anne, 1882-1975; Spingarn, Arthur B. (Arthur Barnett), 1878-1971; Spingarn, Joel Elias, 1875-1939; Tarry, Ellen, 1906-2008; Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-1977; Van Doren, Irita Taylor, 1891-1966; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964; Washington, Booker T., 1856-1915; Wesley, Charles H. (Charles Harris), 1891-1987; White, Walter, 1893-1955; Wilkins, Roy, 1901-1981; Alfred A. Knopf, Inc; American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers; Authors' League of America; Fisk University; Harcourt Brace & Company; Institute of Pacific Relations; Julius Rosenwald Fund; National Association for the Advancement of Colored People; National Conference of Christians and Jews; New York University; Viking Press
- Correspondence, 1896-1972; Series I; 18.14; (46 boxes)
  Arrangement
  The series is organized into four subseries: James Weldon Johnson Correspondence; Grace Nail Johnson Correspondence; Family Correspondence; and Ollie Jewell Sims Okala Correspondence. Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of the writer or addressee of the letter.
  James Weldon Johnson had a long and unique career. For most of his life he was at or near the center of African-American political and cultural activities in the United States, and he counted among his friends and associates many leading blacks and whites who were involved in issues of race relations. His brother, J. Rosamond Johnson, was an important musical comedy performer, appearing in both the United States and Europe, and John B. Nail and John E. Nail, his father-in-law and brother-in-law, were leaders in the social and business life of Harlem. Thus the Johnson correspondence is an important source for African-American history in the first four decades of the twentieth century. Johnson's interests and activities were centered in three principal areas: black literature and music, the political and social advancement of blacks, and education. The correspondence in the Johnson Papers touches most frequently on some aspect of one of these subjects, but also often refers to other facets of African-American life.
  Ollie Jewell Sims Okala's correspondence reflects both her personal and professional life including her relationship with the Johnsons and responsibility for managing the James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson Estate following their deaths.
  It should be noted that folders in the correspondence series do not contain correspondence exclusively. Some folders also contain memoranda, clippings, press releases and other material. In some cases a folder contains only noncorrespondence material; this is indicated by a dash in the "to/from" column.
  N.B. For a more detailed analysis of the subject content of the correspondence see the subject guide in Appendix B. This subject guide was created in 1973 and has been retained for reference.
  - James Weldon Johnson Correspondence, 1896-1972
    Scope and Contents
    The James Weldon Johnson Correspondence is made up of the letters sent and received by James Weldon Johnson and letters received that were addressed jointly to James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson. Grace Nail Johnson's correspondence with publishers and with agents for her husband's books and songs (e.g., Viking Press, ASCAP, etc.) has been treated as a continuation of her husband's correspondence and is included in this subseries.
    In some instances letters from different correspondents have been grouped under a subject heading (e.g. New York University, N.A.A.C.P.). The most important of these subject groupings are the Consular Letter folders which are made up of the letters that Johnson received relating to his consular service and the Haiti folders that bring together Johnson's correspondence with Haitians relative to his investigation in that country.
    Johnson's correspondence was not systematically preserved throughout his career, and the amount of extant material varies for different periods of his life. There is no correspondence for the period before 1904, and between 1906 and 1920 Johnson saved only those letters that he felt were important, but they are substantial in number. They include some of the letters he received while in the consular service, most of the correspondence relating to the publication of his works (including letters of praise and congratulation) and general correspondence with black writers and literary critics. Most of Johnson's official correspondence for the years when he worked for the N.A.A.C.P. is in the Association's files, which are now in the Library of Congress. He did, however, separate his official from his personal correspondence, and the personal correspondence is in the Yale collection. Johnson began systematically to preserve all of his correspondence after he moved to Fisk University in 1931, and most of the letters in the general correspondence series fall in the period beginning in 1931. The correspondence after that date generally includes both incoming letters and copies of his replies.
    African-American literature is one of the subjects most frequently referred to in the correspondence. Johnson, one of the most influential literary figures of his times, was acquainted with most of the black writers and critics who were his contemporaries and often discussed with them aspects of their work or life. He had extensive correspondence with Benjamin Brawley, William Stanley Braithwaite, Sterling Brown, Claude McKay, and Anne Spencer. In addition to black writers and critics, Johnson was acquainted with many white critics and publishers. He corresponded regarding his own work and the work of other black writers. Those with whom he had frequent contact included Marshall Best, Alfred Harcourt, Alfred and Blanche Knopf, H.L. Mencken, Carl Van Doren, Irita Van Doren, Mark Van Doren, and Carl Van Vechten. Johnson's advice was often sought by philanthropic organizations such as the Guggenheim Foundation and the Julius Rosenwald Fund, and his name was frequently used as a reference by young African-Americans applying for grants and fellowships. He became, in effect, an unofficial advisor to the foundations that made such grants. Johnson did not limit his attention to well-known writers, but spent much time giving advice and criticism to aspiring young writers. Advice and comments to such writers figure prominently in the general correspondence.
    Johnson's political activities centered around his association with the N.A.A.C.P. Though the majority of his official correspondence is in the Association's files, he had personal correspondence with all of his co-workers in the National Office and with members of the Board of Directors. Particularly important in this group are Arthur B. Spingarn, Joel E. Spingarn, and Mary White Ovington. After his retirement from the National Office, Johnson's correspondence with workers and board members increased, and it contains much information about the internal working of the Association. Of particular significance is the extensive correspondence with William Pickens, a field secretary, and Walter White, Johnson's successor in the secretaryship. Outside of the Association Johnson was affiliated with Roger N. Baldwin in both the American Fund for Public Service and the American Civil Liberties Union.
    Though his writing and political activities required most of Johnson's time, he maintained throughout his life an interest in education. He was involved in the consolidation of the Atlanta black schools in 1929, and as a member of the Board of Trustees of Atlanta University he participated in the controversy over the selection of a president in 1936. Johnson was also an active member of the Board of Trustees of the Palmer Memorial Institute. In connection with his work for these institutions he had correspondence with many whites and blacks prominent in the field of black education.
    - "Aa-Ak" General (Box 1, Folder 1)
      To: 26 / From: 8
    - Adams, Elbridge L., 1913-26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      General note
      Includes: Villard, Oswald Garrison 0/1 letters with Elbridge L. Adams 1915 Jan 8
      To: 6 / From: 0
    - Adams, Myron W. (Myron Whitlock), 1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      To: 8 / From: 7
    - Addams, Jane, 1925, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      To: 2 / From: 0
    - Adult Education Council of Chicago, 1930-33 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      To: 31 / From: 17
    - Adult Education Council of Chicago, 1933-38 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      To: 47 / From: 34
    - "Al" General (Box 1, Folder 7)
      To: 30 / From: 18
    - Alexander, Lillian A., 1931, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      To: 3 / From: 1
    - Alexander, Will W., 1927-37 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Includes: Nabrit, James M. 0/1 letters (copy) 1936 Jul 1
      To: 14 / From: 12
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc.
      Related Archival Materials note
      See: Alfred A. Knopf, Inc.
    - Allen, B.F., 1916 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      To: 1 / From: 0
    - Allen, Cleveland G., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Am" General (Box 1, Folder 12)
      To: 30 / From: 8
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1931-37, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence with Roger N. Baldwin
      To: 22 / From: 11
    - American Fund for Public Service, 1930-38 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Includes: White, Walter 0/1 letters (copy) with American Fund For Public Service 1933 May 10
      Includes correspondence with Roger N. Baldwin, minutes and memoranda
      To: 19 / From: 3
    - American Shakespeare Foundation, 1928-32 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      To: 18 / From: 10
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers
      - General, 1914-43 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Includes correspondence with GNJ
        To: 21 / From: 1
      - General, 1945-72, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
        Correspondence with GNJ
        To: 28 / From: 2
      - Gene Buck, 1930-42, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Includes: LaGuardia, Fiorello H. 1/0 1936 Jun 10
        To: 12 / From: 3
      - Richard F. Frohlich, 1963-71 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        To: 11 / From: 4
      - Sylvia Rosenberg, 1936-70 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        To: 17 / From: 5
    - "An-Az" General (Box 2, Folder 21)
      To: 39 / From: 22
    - Anderson, Charles W., 1915-26, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
      To: 5 / From: 2
    - Anderson, Sherwood, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Arnett, Trevor, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Arthur, George R. (George Robert), 1931-32 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Associated Negro Press, 1922-38 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Includes correspondence with Claude A. Barnett
      To: 7 / From: 4
    - Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, Inc., 1934-37 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      To: 4 / From: 3
    - Atlanta University, 1929-36 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      To: 12 / From: 8
    - Author's League of America, 1931-38, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
      To: 16 / From: 6
    - Azikiwe, Nnamdi, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      To: 1 / From: 1
    - "Ba-Bd" General (Box 2, Folder 31)
      To: 36 / From: 25
    - Bagnall, Robert W., 1929-38 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      To: 7 / From: 2
    - Baker, Jacob, 1928-36 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      To: 4 / From: 2
    - Baldwin, Roger N. (Roger Nash)
      See: American Civil Liberties Union American Fund for Public Service, Box 1, folder 13
    - Ballou, Robert O. (Robert Oleson), 1929-35 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Baltimore City-Wide Young Peoples' Forum, 1933-35 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Includes: Mitchell, Mrs. Clarence M. 5/9 letters 1934 Feb 19 - 1935 Apr 1
      Includes correspondence with Juanita E. Jackson To: 5 / From: 9 letters
      To: 20 / From: 15
    - Baltimore Open Forum, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      To: 5 / From: 5
    - Banks, W. Rutherford, 1929-38 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      Includes correspondence with Mrs. W.R. Banks
      To: 16 / From: 10
    - Barnett, Albert E., 1933, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      Includes: White, Walter 1/0 letters (copy) with Albert E. Barnett 1935 Jul 24
    - Barnett, Claude A.
      See: Associated Negro Press, Box 2, folder 26
    - Battle, Effie R., 1934, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Bauman and Hero, 1930-34 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      To: 13 / From: 5
    - "Be-Bh" General (Box 3, Folder 41)
      To: 32 / From: 25
    - Beittel, A.D., 1932-38 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      To: 8 / From: 5
    - Bellegrade, Auguste D., 1932, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      To: 2 / From: 3
    - Bennett, Gwendolyn, 1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bethune, Mary McLeod, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - "Bi-Bq" General (Box 3, Folder 46)
      To: 37 / From: 25
    - Blanchet, Albert, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bok, Edward William, 1913, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      To: 4 / From: 0
    - Bond, Horace Mann, 1934, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      To: 3 / From: 3
    - Bontemps, Arna Wendell, 1936, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
      To: 3 / From: 0
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, 1936, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      To: 11 / From: 8
    - Bowles, Luanna J., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Boyle, Louise, 1918, 1925, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
      To: 5 / From: 0
    - "Br-Brom" General (Box 3, Folder 54)
      To: 30 / From: 19
    - Braithwaite, William Stanley, 1913-34 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      To: 25 / From: 8
    - Brandt, Zelma Corning, 1926, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Brawley, Benjamin Griffith, 1916-34 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      To: 23 / From: 7
    - Brentano's Inc., 1924 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      To: 3 / From: 4
    - Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      Includes leaflet of poetry
    - Brooks, Jonathan Henderson, 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Brookwood Labor School, 1931-34 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Broun, Heywood, 1924-34, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
      Includes correspondence re: Broun
      To: 3 / From: 6
    - "Brow-Bt" General (Box 4, Folder 63)
      To: 24 / From: 18
    - Brown, Charlotte Hawkins, 1931-36 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Brown, Francis J. (Francis James), 1935-38 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      To: 9 / From: 5
    - Brown, Sterling Allen, 1930-37, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
      To: 13 / From: 7
    - Browne, Marie Joe, 1934-37, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
      To: 28 / From: 6
    - Brownlee, Frederick Leslie, 1933-37 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      To: 15 / From: 12
    - Bruce, Roscoe Conkling, 1926-33 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Includes correspondence re: Bruce
      To: 6 / From: 1
    - Bryan, Helen R., 1930-34, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
      Includes: Johnson, Charles S. 1/0 letters (copy) with Helen R. Bryan 1932 Dec 16
      Includes: Johnson, Mordecai W. 1/0 letters (copy) with Helen R. Bryan 1933 Jan 6
      To: 36 / From: 9
    - Bryan, William Jennings, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - "Bu-Bz" General (Box 4, Folder 72)
      To: 30 / From: 17
    - Buck, Gene
      See: ASCAP, Box 2, folder 16
    - Bumstead, Horace, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Bunch, Ralph J., 1931-32 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      To: 2 / From: 2
    - Burleigh, Harry T., undated (Box 4, Folder 75)
      Christmas card
    - Burroughs, Nannie Helen, 1931-38, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
      To: 5 / From: 3
    - Buttitta, Anthony J., 1931-34, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
      To: 9 / From: 3
    - Bynner, Witter, 1925, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - "Ca-Cd" General (Box 4, Folder 79)
      To: 36 / From: 19
    - Calling Cards, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin N. (Benjamin Nathan), 1929-32 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Carr, Wilbur J., 1912-33 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      To: 8 / From: 4
    - Carter, Edward C. (Edward Clark)